{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x - 10\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "14x - 12", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (8x - 2) + (6x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 10\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -9x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-13x - 3", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-4x - 10) + (-9x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x - 10\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x - 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-8x - 17", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (2x - 10) + (-10x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x - 6\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x + 1", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (5x - 6) + (-6x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -7x - 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-17x - 5", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-10x + 2) + (-7x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 6\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 10\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-4x - 16", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-2x - 6) + (-2x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x - 6\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x - 2", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (4x - 6) + (-3x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x - 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "16x - 3", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (7x - 2) + (9x - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x + 6\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-8x + 10", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-7x + 6) + (-x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x - 9", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-10) + (4x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "9x + 5", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6x - 2) + (3x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x + 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 10\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x - 8", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (9x + 2) + (-5x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 10\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x - 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-11x - 14", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-5x - 10) + (-6x - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "7x + 12", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (5) + (7x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 5x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "11x + 6", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6x + 5) + (5x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "6x + 4", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (9x + 9) + (-3x - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-9x - 2", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-5x - 3) + (-4x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x + 7", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9) + (x - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "8x + 13", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (8x + 9) + (4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 6\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-5x - 1", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-9x - 7) + (4x + 6)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 8\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x - 7", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-3x + 1) + (2x - 8)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "12x + 2", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (5x - 7) + (7x + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-4x - 12", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-10x - 7) + (6x - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-17x - 5", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-7x - 3) + (-10x - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x + 3\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "8x + 8", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-x + 5) + (9x + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x - 2", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (7x - 3) + (-6x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -7x + 6\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-15x + 3", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-8x - 3) + (-7x + 6)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 5x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x + 2", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-4x + 1) + (5x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x + 4", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (x + 9) + (3x - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -7x - 10\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-16x - 1", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-9x + 9) + (-7x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -9x - 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-12x - 7", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-3x - 3) + (-9x - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-5x - 1", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (1) + (-5x - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "5", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6x + 1) + (-6x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-7x - 6", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-6x - 7) + (-x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-3x + 8", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-x + 1) + (-2x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-8x + 14", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5) + (-10x + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "17x", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (8x + 5) + (9x - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x - 8\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-10x - 11", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-4x - 3) + (-6x - 8)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -8x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-7x + 3", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (x + 5) + (-8x - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x - 6", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (5x + 1) + (-4x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 6\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-15x + 15", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-10x + 9) + (-5x + 6)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-2x + 5", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-2x + 1) + (4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x + 18", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9) + (-x + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "10x + 9", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (7x + 5) + (3x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 10\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-7x - 17", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-8x - 7) + (x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 3\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x - 8", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6x - 5) + (-2x - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-12x - 3", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-9x - 5) + (-3x + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x - 3\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x - 4", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-5x - 1) + (9x - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 8x + 3\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "8x + 10", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (7) + (8x + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -7x\\). Find \\((f+g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x - 1", "explanation": "(f+g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (8x - 1) + (-7x)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 10\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -7x - 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "8x - 6", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (x - 10) - (-7x - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -9x + 2\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "15x - 4", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (6x - 2) - (-9x + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 1\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-2x + 2", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-6x + 1) - (-4x - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 5\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x + 4", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-x + 9) - (-5x + 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 8\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x - 15", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (3x - 7) - (-x + 8)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "10x", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (8x - 7) - (-2x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x + 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-4x + 5", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-6x + 9) - (-2x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x - 10\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x + 7", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-x - 3) - (-3x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x + 8", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1) - (x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -1\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "8x + 10", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (8x + 9) - (-1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 5x - 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-9x - 3", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-4x - 7) - (5x - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 2\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-3x - 1", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (x + 1) - (4x + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x + 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "9x + 1", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (5x + 5) - (-4x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x - 10\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-16x + 3", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-10x - 7) - (6x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x - 10", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-2x - 3) - (-x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x - 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "14x + 11", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (4x + 4) - (-10x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "5x + 2", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (7x + 9) - (2x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x + 1\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-8x - 4", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-7x - 3) - (x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 0\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x - 2\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-6x + 2", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (0) - (6x - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x + 4", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (6x + 8) - (4x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x - 1\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-7", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (9x - 8) - (9x - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x + 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-12x - 4", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-5x) - (7x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 5x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-6", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (5x + 1) - (5x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-5x + 16", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-10x + 9) - (-5x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x - 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-13x + 9", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-6x + 5) - (7x - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x + 2\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-7x - 9", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-x - 7) - (6x + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -9x - 1\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "16x + 6", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (7x + 5) - (-9x - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x + 5\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-7x + 5) - (-10x + 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x - 1\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x + 10", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-4x + 9) - (-6x - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -8x - 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "10x + 4", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (2x - 3) - (-8x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 10\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "11x + 19", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (9x + 9) - (-2x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x + 13", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-5x + 9) - (-4x - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 8x - 10\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-10x + 3", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-2x - 7) - (8x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x - 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "5x + 5", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1) - (-x - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -8x - 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "0", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-8x - 7) - (-8x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-6x - 14", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-3x - 7) - (3x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 2\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "5x - 5", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-3) - (-5x + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -7x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "13x - 2", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (6x + 5) - (-7x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-3x - 7", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-9x) - (-6x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 5x - 8\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-8x + 16", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-3x + 8) - (5x - 8)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x - 3", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (4) - (-3x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "10x - 1", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (6x - 8) - (-4x - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 10\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-7x + 14", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-6x + 4) - (x - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-x - 8) - (-x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 2\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x + 10", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (2x + 8) - (3x - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 4\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "6x - 8", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (8x - 4) - (2x + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x + 1\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-11x + 7", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (-4x + 8) - (7x + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x + 7\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-5x + 1", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (x + 8) - (6x + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x + 9\\). Find \\((f-g)(x)\\)", "answer": "15x - 17", "explanation": "(f-g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f-g)(x) \u003d (5x - 8) - (-10x + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f-g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-6x^2 + 3x + 3", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3x + 3)(2x + 1)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x - 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x^2 + 8x - 16", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3x + 4)(-x - 4)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-8x^2 - 24x - 16", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4x - 4)(2x + 4)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x^2 + 4x", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)(x)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x^2 + 11x + 6", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-x - 2)(-4x - 3)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "25x^2 + 5x - 12", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5x - 4)(-5x + 3)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x - 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x^2 + 8x", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2x)(-x - 4)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-9x^2 + 3x", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3x)(-3x + 1)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x^2 + 2x - 4", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)(2x - 2)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x + 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-3x^2 - 12x", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3x)(x + 4)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "0x^2 + 12x - 12", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4)(3x - 3)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-16x^2 + 4x + 12", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4x + 4)(4x + 3)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-9x^2 + 12x", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3x - 4)(-3x)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x^2 - 7x - 20", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-x + 4)(-3x - 5)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x + 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x^2 - 4x - 8", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2x - 2)(-2x + 4)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x^2 - 12x - 15", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3x + 3)(x - 5)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x^2 - 20x + 25", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (2x - 5)(2x - 5)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "25x^2 + 35x + 12", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5x - 3)(-5x - 4)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x^2 - 18x - 10", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (x - 5)(4x + 2)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-8x^2 - 10x + 3", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4x - 1)(-2x - 3)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-4x^2 + 4x - 1", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2x + 1)(2x - 1)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x^2 + 8x - 3", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3x - 1)(x + 3)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(x)\\)", "answer": "15x^2 - 9x - 6", "explanation": "(f*g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3x + 3)(-5x - 2)\nSimplify using the FOIL method", "prompt": "(f*g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x^2 - 5x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "9x - 5", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (9x^2 - 5x)/(x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x^2 - x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "9x + 1", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-9x^2 - x)/(-x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -12x^2 - 16x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-3x - 4", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-12x^2 - 16x)/(4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x^2 + 6x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-2x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-6x^2 + 6x)/(3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 12x^2 + 15x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-4x - 5", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (12x^2 + 15x)/(-3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 12x^2 - 4x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-3x + 1", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (12x^2 - 4x)/(-4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x^2 - 5x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x - 5", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-x^2 - 5x)/(x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x^2 + 28x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-2x + 7", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-8x^2 + 28x)/(4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x^2 + 4x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-2x^2 + 4x)/(2x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x^2 + 15x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x - 5", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-6x^2 + 15x)/(-3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x^2 - 4x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "2x + 1", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-8x^2 - 4x)/(-4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x^2 - 14x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x + 7", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-2x^2 - 14x)/(-2x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x^2 - 6x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-3x^2 - 6x)/(-3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -14x^2 - 6x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "7x + 3", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-14x^2 - 6x)/(-2x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x^2 + 2x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "6x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (6x^2 + 2x)/(x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 36x^2 - 12x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "9x - 3", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (36x^2 - 12x)/(4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -45x^2 - 15x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "9x + 3", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-45x^2 - 15x)/(-5x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -24x^2 + 12x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "8x - 4", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-24x^2 + 12x)/(-3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -40x^2 - 10x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "8x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-40x^2 - 10x)/(-5x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x^2 - 2x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-4x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (4x^2 - 2x)/(-x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x^2 + 12x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-2x - 4", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (6x^2 + 12x)/(-3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x^2 - 12x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x - 4", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-3x^2 - 12x)/(3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x^2 + 8x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "-x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-4x^2 + 8x)/(4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x^2 + 4x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x - 4", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-x^2 + 4x)/(-x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x^2 - 4x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-2x^2 - 4x)/(-2x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 12x^2 - 15x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x - 5", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (12x^2 - 15x)/(3x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 10x^2 + 6x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "5x + 3", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (10x^2 + 6x)/(2x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -12x^2 + 16x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "3x - 4", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (-12x^2 + 16x)/(-4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 16x^2 + 8x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x\\). Find \\((f/g)(x)\\)", "answer": "4x + 2", "explanation": "(f/g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\nPlug in the value for f(x) and g(x)\n(f/g)(x) \u003d (16x^2 + 8x)/(4x)\nSimplify using the distributive property", "prompt": "(f/g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "26", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) + g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-10*-4 + 4) + (4*-4 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(-5)\\)", "answer": "6", "explanation": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d f(-5) + g(-5)\nPlug in the value for f(-5) and g(-5)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-5*-5 - 8) + (3*-5 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 8x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(7)\\)", "answer": "74", "explanation": "(f+g)(7) \u003d f(7) + g(7)\nPlug in the value for f(7) and g(7)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (3*7 - 4) + (8*7 + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(7) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x + 6\\). Find \\((f+g)(-6)\\)", "answer": "-74", "explanation": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d f(-6) + g(-6)\nPlug in the value for f(-6) and g(-6)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (8*-6 + 4) + (6*-6 + 6)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(1)\\)", "answer": "-9", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) + g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-8+ 8) + (-10+ 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(8)\\)", "answer": "39", "explanation": "(f+g)(8) \u003d f(8) + g(8)\nPlug in the value for f(8) and g(8)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-3*8 - 4) + (9*8 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(8) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(9)\\)", "answer": "51", "explanation": "(f+g)(9) \u003d f(9) + g(9)\nPlug in the value for f(9) and g(9)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-4*9 + 8) + (9*9 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(9) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 8x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "-28", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) + g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (2*-4 + 8) + (8*-4 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(2)\\)", "answer": "3", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) + g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-1*2 + 4) + (-4*2 + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -6x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(9)\\)", "answer": "-31", "explanation": "(f+g)(9) \u003d f(9) + g(9)\nPlug in the value for f(9) and g(9)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (4*9 - 8) + (-6*9 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(9) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(-6)\\)", "answer": "-17", "explanation": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d f(-6) + g(-6)\nPlug in the value for f(-6) and g(-6)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-6 + 8) + (2*-6 - 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x + 6\\). Find \\((f+g)(-7)\\)", "answer": "-47", "explanation": "(f+g)(-7) \u003d f(-7) + g(-7)\nPlug in the value for f(-7) and g(-7)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6*-7 - 4) + (-7 + 6)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-7) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(5)\\)", "answer": "12", "explanation": "(f+g)(5) \u003d f(5) + g(5)\nPlug in the value for f(5) and g(5)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-6*5 + 8) + (6*5 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(-8)\\)", "answer": "-15", "explanation": "(f+g)(-8) \u003d f(-8) + g(-8)\nPlug in the value for f(-8) and g(-8)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (0*-8 + 8) + (4*-8 + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-8) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(7)\\)", "answer": "-4", "explanation": "(f+g)(7) \u003d f(7) + g(7)\nPlug in the value for f(7) and g(7)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (3*7 - 8) + (-3*7 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(7) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 10\\). Find \\((f+g)(6)\\)", "answer": "14", "explanation": "(f+g)(6) \u003d f(6) + g(6)\nPlug in the value for f(6) and g(6)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (9*6) + (-5*6 - 10)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(6) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -7x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(5)\\)", "answer": "-49", "explanation": "(f+g)(5) \u003d f(5) + g(5)\nPlug in the value for f(5) and g(5)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-1*5 - 7) + (-7*5 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "-4", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) + g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (8*-2 - 3) + (-4*-2 + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "20", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) + g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-5*-2 + 8) + (-2 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(-3)\\)", "answer": "5", "explanation": "(f+g)(-3) \u003d f(-3) + g(-3)\nPlug in the value for f(-3) and g(-3)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-3 - 4) + (-1*-3 + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(5)\\)", "answer": "-47", "explanation": "(f+g)(5) \u003d f(5) + g(5)\nPlug in the value for f(5) and g(5)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (5) + (-10*5 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(3)\\)", "answer": "11", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) + g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-3*3 - 8) + (7*3 + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "-25", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) + g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6*-4 - 4) + (-2*-4 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(3)\\)", "answer": "-28", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) + g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-8*3 + 4) + (-3*3 + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(-5)\\)", "answer": "-16", "explanation": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d f(-5) + g(-5)\nPlug in the value for f(-5) and g(-5)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (- 4) + (2*-5 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(-6)\\)", "answer": "-30", "explanation": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d f(-6) + g(-6)\nPlug in the value for f(-6) and g(-6)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (5*-6 - 4) + (4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 8\\). Find \\((f+g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "12", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) + g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-6*-4 + 8) + (3*-4 - 8)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -8x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(4)\\)", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "(f+g)(4) \u003d f(4) + g(4)\nPlug in the value for f(4) and g(4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (4*4 + 9) + (-8*4 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -9x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(3)\\)", "answer": "-59", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) + g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-10*3 - 3) + (-9*3 + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(-3)\\)", "answer": "9", "explanation": "(f+g)(-3) \u003d f(-3) + g(-3)\nPlug in the value for f(-3) and g(-3)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-7*-3 + 1) + (3*-3 - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 9\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(4)\\)", "answer": "15", "explanation": "(f+g)(4) \u003d f(4) + g(4)\nPlug in the value for f(4) and g(4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-1*4 + 9) + (2*4 + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 7\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x - 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "-60", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) + g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6*-4 - 7) + (7*-4 - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x - 8\\). Find \\((f+g)(-5)\\)", "answer": "3", "explanation": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d f(-5) + g(-5)\nPlug in the value for f(-5) and g(-5)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-8*-5 + 1) + (6*-5 - 8)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x + 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -10x + 7\\). Find \\((f+g)(-10)\\)", "answer": "162", "explanation": "(f+g)(-10) \u003d f(-10) + g(-10)\nPlug in the value for f(-10) and g(-10)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-5*-10 + 5) + (-10*-10 + 7)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-10) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -9x + 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(2)\\)", "answer": "1", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) + g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (5*2 + 8) + (-9*2 + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(-6)\\)", "answer": "56", "explanation": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d f(-6) + g(-6)\nPlug in the value for f(-6) and g(-6)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-7*-6 - 8) + (-4*-6 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 4\\). Find \\((f+g)(1)\\)", "answer": "-3", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) + g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-2*1) + (-5+ 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 6\\). Find \\((f+g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "6", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) + g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (2*-4 + 4) + (-1*-4 + 6)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 8\\). Find \\((f+g)(-5)\\)", "answer": "-41", "explanation": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d f(-5) + g(-5)\nPlug in the value for f(-5) and g(-5)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (7*-5 - 8) + (-2*-5 - 8)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(7)\\)", "answer": "-9", "explanation": "(f+g)(7) \u003d f(7) + g(7)\nPlug in the value for f(7) and g(7)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-5*7 - 4) + (3*7 + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(7) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(-6)\\)", "answer": "-19", "explanation": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d f(-6) + g(-6)\nPlug in the value for f(-6) and g(-6)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-6 + 4) + (2*-6 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-6) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 6x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(0)\\)", "answer": "17", "explanation": "(f+g)(0) \u003d f(0) + g(0)\nPlug in the value for f(0) and g(0)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (4*0 + 8) + (6*0 + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(0) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 3\\). Find \\((f+g)(7)\\)", "answer": "-31", "explanation": "(f+g)(7) \u003d f(7) + g(7)\nPlug in the value for f(7) and g(7)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-10*7 + 8) + (4*7 + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(7) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 9x\\). Find \\((f+g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "-6", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) + g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-3*-1) + (9*-1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 8x + 6\\). Find \\((f+g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "-8", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) + g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (3*-2 + 8) + (8*-2 + 6)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 8\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 1\\). Find \\((f+g)(-7)\\)", "answer": "-49", "explanation": "(f+g)(-7) \u003d f(-7) + g(-7)\nPlug in the value for f(-7) and g(-7)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (6*-7 - 8) + (1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(-7) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 8x + 9\\). Find \\((f+g)(8)\\)", "answer": "89", "explanation": "(f+g)(8) \u003d f(8) + g(8)\nPlug in the value for f(8) and g(8)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (2*8) + (8*8 + 9)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(8) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 7x - 5\\). Find \\((f+g)(7)\\)", "answer": "93", "explanation": "(f+g)(7) \u003d f(7) + g(7)\nPlug in the value for f(7) and g(7)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (7*7) + (7*7 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(7) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -9x - 2\\). Find \\((f+g)(1)\\)", "answer": "-16", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) + g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f+g)(x) \u003d (-9+ 4) + (-9- 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f+g)(1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "-28", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) * g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-1*-4 + 3) * (2*-4 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "7", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) * g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3*-2 - 5) * (-3*-2 + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x + 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(1)\\)", "answer": "0", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) * g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4- 1) * (-2+ 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "20", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) * g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (2*-1 - 3) * (-1*-1 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(-3)\\)", "answer": "10", "explanation": "(f+g)(-3) \u003d f(-3) * g(-3)\nPlug in the value for f(-3) and g(-3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4*-3 - 2) * (-2*-3 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x + 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "2", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) * g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4*-1 + 2) * (3*-1 + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "-10", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) * g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-1*-2) * (-2 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x\\). Find \\((f*g)(2)\\)", "answer": "60", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) * g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3*2 + 4) * (3*2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x - 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(2)\\)", "answer": "0", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) * g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2*2 + 4) * (4*2 - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(3)\\)", "answer": "96", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) * g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4*3 - 4) * (-3*3 + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(0)\\)", "answer": "-3", "explanation": "(f+g)(0) \u003d f(0) * g(0)\nPlug in the value for f(0) and g(0)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (2*0 + 3) * (-2*0 - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(0) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(-5)\\)", "answer": "69", "explanation": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d f(-5) * g(-5)\nPlug in the value for f(-5) and g(-5)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5*-5 - 2) * (0*-5 + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(4)\\)", "answer": "-14", "explanation": "(f+g)(4) \u003d f(4) * g(4)\nPlug in the value for f(4) and g(4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4 - 2) * (-1*4 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x + 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "-84", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) * g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2*-4 - 1) * (4*-4 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x\\). Find \\((f*g)(3)\\)", "answer": "54", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) * g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4*3 - 3) * (2*3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "-4", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) * g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3*-1 + 1) * (-4*-1 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x - 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(2)\\)", "answer": "63", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) * g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2*2 - 3) * (-4*2 - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(1)\\)", "answer": "1", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) * g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4- 5) * (4- 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x\\). Find \\((f*g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "44", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) * g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3*-4 - 1) * (-1*-4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(4)\\)", "answer": "-17", "explanation": "(f+g)(4) \u003d f(4) * g(4)\nPlug in the value for f(4) and g(4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4*4 - 1) * (4 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "55", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) * g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-1*-2 + 3) * (-5*-2 + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "-121", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) * g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5*-2 + 1) * (4*-2 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "-35", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) * g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (2*-1 - 5) * (-1*-1 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x + 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(3)\\)", "answer": "0", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) * g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3 - 3) * (-1*3 + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 2\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(2)\\)", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) * g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5*2 - 2) * (3*2 - 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(1)\\)", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) * g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (- 4) * (2+ 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(-5)\\)", "answer": "120", "explanation": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d f(-5) * g(-5)\nPlug in the value for f(-5) and g(-5)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-1*-5) * (-5*-5 - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x + 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(0)\\)", "answer": "-2", "explanation": "(f+g)(0) \u003d f(0) * g(0)\nPlug in the value for f(0) and g(0)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-1*0 - 1) * (2*0 + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(0) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "-20", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) * g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5*-1 - 1) * (3*-1 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(4)\\)", "answer": "85", "explanation": "(f+g)(4) \u003d f(4) * g(4)\nPlug in the value for f(4) and g(4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2*4 + 3) * (-5*4 + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x - 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(3)\\)", "answer": "104", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) * g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4*3 + 1) * (3*3 - 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(-5)\\)", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "(f+g)(-5) \u003d f(-5) * g(-5)\nPlug in the value for f(-5) and g(-5)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5 + 3) * (-2*-5 - 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-5) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3x\\). Find \\((f*g)(2)\\)", "answer": "18", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) * g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-3*2 + 3) * (-3*2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(-3)\\)", "answer": "-180", "explanation": "(f+g)(-3) \u003d f(-3) * g(-3)\nPlug in the value for f(-3) and g(-3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (4*-3 - 3) * (-5*-3 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 3x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(4)\\)", "answer": "-105", "explanation": "(f+g)(4) \u003d f(4) * g(4)\nPlug in the value for f(4) and g(4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-1*4 - 3) * (3*4 + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x - 5\\). Find \\((f*g)(1)\\)", "answer": "-28", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) * g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3+ 1) * (-2- 5)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -4x + 1\\). Find \\((f*g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "27", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) * g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2*-2 - 1) * (-4*-2 + 1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x - 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(0)\\)", "answer": "-6", "explanation": "(f+g)(0) \u003d f(0) * g(0)\nPlug in the value for f(0) and g(0)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4*0 + 3) * (0 - 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(0) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "0", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) * g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-1 + 1) * (0*-1 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 2x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(3)\\)", "answer": "-60", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) * g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5*3 - 5) * (2*3 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d x + 2\\). Find \\((f*g)(3)\\)", "answer": "15", "explanation": "(f+g)(3) \u003d f(3) * g(3)\nPlug in the value for f(3) and g(3)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (0*3 + 3) * (3 + 2)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(3) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -3\\). Find \\((f*g)(2)\\)", "answer": "39", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) * g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-5*2 - 3) * (0*2 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(-1)\\)", "answer": "-15", "explanation": "(f+g)(-1) \u003d f(-1) * g(-1)\nPlug in the value for f(-1) and g(-1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (0*-1 - 3) * (-2*-1 + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-1) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -5x + 4\\). Find \\((f*g)(2)\\)", "answer": "-42", "explanation": "(f+g)(2) \u003d f(2) * g(2)\nPlug in the value for f(2) and g(2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (3*2 + 1) * (-5*2 + 4)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 5\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -x - 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(-2)\\)", "answer": "-3", "explanation": "(f+g)(-2) \u003d f(-2) * g(-2)\nPlug in the value for f(-2) and g(-2)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-4*-2 - 5) * (-1*-2 - 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-2) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 3\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d -2x + 3\\). Find \\((f*g)(-4)\\)", "answer": "-55", "explanation": "(f+g)(-4) \u003d f(-4) * g(-4)\nPlug in the value for f(-4) and g(-4)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (2*-4 + 3) * (-2*-4 + 3)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(-4) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 1\\) and \\(g(x) \u003d 4x\\). Find \\((f*g)(1)\\)", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "(f+g)(1) \u003d f(1) * g(1)\nPlug in the value for f(1) and g(1)\n(f*g)(x) \u003d (-2- 1) * (4*1)\nSimplify", "prompt": "(f*g)(1) \u003d"}
]}